

CONTACT ME AT

- diego.alexander.diaz@correou nivalle.edu.co
- https://github.com/diegodh1
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/diego-alexander-4a625b195/
- https://www.hackerrank.com/diegodiazh1994

SKILLS SUMMARY

- • • English
- • • Kotlin Android Studio
- • • Golang
- • • Java
- • • SQL (postgres, Sql Server)
- • • Rest Api
- • • Mobile Applications
- • • Data structure and Analysis and design of algorithms

AWARDS RECEIVED

- four times among the top five students of the semester
- Best integrapps employee

COURSES AND CERTIFICATES

Mathematics for Machine Learning: Multivariate Calculus.

https://coursera.org/share/365 af671e2ed08b36c22fccf9906f5c

Concurrency in Go. Link https://coursera.org/share/5a9 8cfec33c91f3be536ddd1069895

DIEGO DÍAZ HERNÁNDEZ

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a software developer and student in last semesters, with experience in mobile applications and backend services. Beyond of the programming language I consider the most important for a software developer is the hability to solve problems and learn about the new tecnologies In my free time I love playing soccer, jogging, read about different topics of my career like IA, concurrent programming, DP, etc.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Backend developer

Spataro Nápoli S.A | Dec 2016 - Dec 2018

- Build differents Api Rest Services for using Golang with gorilla mux.
- Perform different queries in SQL to obtain the information necessary for the analysis of business data.

Mobile Developer, Backend Developer

Integrapps S.A | Dec 2018 - Present

- Build complex projects from start to finish for differents companies in my region such as Sidoc S.A, Celco, Hercules, Curaduria Urbana 3.
- Build mobile applications whose main objective is to solve the problems of the production plant.

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

Universidad del Valle. Cali, Colombia.

Major in Computer Science Engineer | Jan 2017 - Present

- Studied project planning, coordination, and ethics
- Worked with various startups on launching new apps and services